LADY LINDBURG!
are you hurt no i managed to make
it i'm so terribly sorry it's my
mistake i should have come with you
m 'lady there's no point in having an
escort during my trials for the
right to the throne i'm the one who
insisted on that you are not at fault
inez i'm sorry i didn't mean to make
you worry.
Lady Lindbergh.
Lord Darkin.
Let us return to the castle.
Lord Rain would
like to speak with you
as soon as possible.
I understand.
But I can't take it.
If my heart comes, I can't take it.
I can't take it.
What I can't see.
What I want to see?
I will rush with my dreams.
I can't take it.
I've spoken with Lin.
Is it true?
Was a Minotaur actually summoned
to a city full of people?
It resides in the abyss, the
deepest parts of the dungeon.
There is no doubt, sir.
In other words, this is the
work of someone's intent.
It seems so.
The source of the summon is
thought to be a mysterious
ring found on the corpse of a
merchant lying at the scene.
When Oaken did his research,
he found the magic stone in the ring
is of a surprisingly high purity.
It is not something that you
would normally find on the market.
Minotaurs are a threat A-level demon.
Normal people cannot simply just buy
something to trap a creature like that.
According to what Okun says,
the crest left on the
stone indicates the ring
originates from the
Magic Empire of Doritis.
Of course it was Doritis.
He has often provoked us,
but it's different this time.
Right.
He tried to ensure it would work by binding
the princess at the time of the summon.
Plus, he isn't even trying
to get rid of the evidence.
It's troubling.
A plot to assassinate Princess Lindbergh
is bad enough, but there seems to be more.
He was waiting for us to initiate a war.
It seems they want nothing
more than to take what is ours.
Our kingdom's prized resource the
relics of the dungeon of the lost.
Now then about the man who was
able to save lynn's life with a
single broadsword and in only a
few seconds he defeated a minotaur.
Afterwards the secret core followed
his movements but lost sight of him.
They said he disappeared before their
very eyes like some sort of an illusion.
Unbelievable.
Just who is this man?
Noor!
You survived!
Huh?
Survived what?
Don't act like you don't know.
Last night, a giant demon appeared
near the entrance of the dungeon.
It was a beast like nothing
we've ever seen around here.
Really?
It was over by the construction site.
And since we didn't see you come
by after work, I got worried.
Sorry about that.
Last night I was being followed
around by a shady group of characters.
So I ducked and hid and went home.
Wait, are you serious?
Then why is your face dirty?
Oh, well, I still had to clean
the mud out of the drains.
In any case,
you're real lucky you didn't bump into
that thing while you were out last night.
I used to be an A-Rank myself, and if I
came across him, I'd be dead for sure.
Sounds like the demon was
really something awful.
Sure glad I only had to
deal with a surly cow.
So, uh, what happened to the demon?
Well, it seems it was taken down
by a mystery man with a broadsword,
apparently in one blow, too.
Wow.
It's a good thing there are people
out there who take care of us.
Here, your payment for yesterday's work.
Okay, thanks a lot.
So, are you still not trying
to get yourself a decent job?
A decent job?
I'm already working as
an adventurer, aren't I?
Come on, Nor.
I keep telling you, you
could earn 30 % more.
You don't need me taking
a cut of your cash.
I have found you. Huh?
At long last.
You're from last night. What?
I'm sorry for following you
around, but I needed to meet you.
So I used my long-distance detection
skill to find out where you were.
Oh, I've heard of that.
So then your job class is listed as Thief.
No, my focus is the Magician class.
But I also have some knowledge
of all six skill systems.
Huh?
That's impressive.
They're all just at a basic level, though.
Actually so basic, it's
embarrassing telling you about them.
Uh, you can't possibly mean that.
Hey, is that him? Can't be.
Uh, we've got an audience here, so
would you mind speaking outside?
What did you do, Nor?
Nothing, I promise.
At least nothing that I can
think of to get me in trouble.
There shouldn't be too
many folks out right now.
And plus,
my sound-proofing and concealment skill
can keep people from eavesdropping.
Should I go with her, or what should I do?
Get out there, so that you don't
make any more dumb mistakes. What?
Not sure what you mean, but all right.
Man, are we sure that guy actually exists?
If the Secret Corps couldn't
find him, how are we supposed to?
I mean, seriously.
Seems like they might
be looking for someone.
Don't worry about them.
They can't see us.
I do apologize for just
showing up out of nowhere.
I shouldn't have confronted you while
you were speaking with the Guildmaster.
Oh no, don't worry. That's no big deal.
So what is it that I can help you with?
I wanted to properly give you my thanks.
I truly appreciate it.
You saved my very life last night.
And it's not just because
you saved my life.
What you did amounts to saving the
lives of many others in this nation.
Oh no, please.
Your skills are far more
impressive than mine could ever be.
To be honest, I think I may
have just gotten in your way.
That is simply not true! I mean,
I can't imagine what would have happened
to me if you had not rushed to my defense!
Oh, um, then I humbly accept
your thanks. Personally,
I am obligated to give
you as much of a reward as
possible for your assistance
with what happened last night.
I want to greatly compensate
you with my deepest gratitude.
Yeah, well, your gratitude has
already been more than enough.
So can we maybe just
call everything square?
No, sorry.
Please let me thank you properly.
My father has also asked to meet you so
he can give you his full appreciation.
I don't think that's
going to be necessary.
I may not look it, but
I'm a person of status.
I must give something to the
person who I owe my very life to.
Look, I don't need anything.
But there must be something that
you're having trouble with, right?
Nothing that I can think of.
If you need, I can even talk to my
father about some territory that...
I'm sorry, but I'm good.
I need nothing more.
But I want to.
Please don't cry.
This can't happen.
You have an obligation to
accept my gratitude. I did.
I will not move an inch until you
are willing to accept my gratitude.
I will not leave this spot until
you agree to train me in your art!
Okay, look, if I agree to meet with
your father, will that be enough?
Great! That's wonderful!
But there's no need for
anything extravagant, alright?
Okay, now then, if you'd be so kind, please
follow close behind me. Oh, right now?
Yes.
I don't want people to
spot us going inside,
So I'll use my concealment detection
occlusion and multiple others to hide us.
This place is massive!
Is this your house?
Yes, I know. I know.
It may seem a bit ostentatious
and everything, but come on in.
Now that I think of it, I'm afraid you
still haven't told me what your name is yet.
Oh, right. I'm Noor.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Lord Noor.
And what's your name?
My full apologies!
I completely forgot to introduce myself!
I am Lindbergh Clays at your service.
But my full title can be a little
cumbersome and pretentious,
so I just go by Lind for the most part.
So you can feel free to just
use that whenever you want.
Man, this is really a spacious house.
She must be one of those
fancy aristocrats or whatever.
So that you don't make
any more dumb mistakes.
Is this what he meant?
Oh!
Perfect!
We can ask her where
my father is right now.
Welcome back home, Lady Lindberg.
Hello, Ines.
I would like to speak
with my father, please.
He is currently in the audience
chamber speaking with Rain, m 'lady.
Who is this man with you?
This man is my honored guest.
He's the one who risked his life to
save mine in that attack last night.
We are in your debt. Follow
me. I'll lead the way.
She must be the maid.
Gotta be hard to do laundry
and dishes in that outfit.
She might want to rethink that.
Oh, she seems super suspicious of me.
Uh, what's going on Ines? What's all this?
And why is Lindbergh with you?
I'm not sure I like this place.
Who might this man be?
That's enough, Gilbert.
Now step aside.
This person is an honored guest
of Lady Lindbergh. Ah, yes.
I can only guess if you're
here with Lady Lindbergh.
Then you're the one we've
all been talking about.
Hmm.
You sure don't look
like very much, do you?
Stop being a nuisance, Gilbert.
Also, come along with us to the chambers.
The more escorts, the better.
Oh, okay. I'll go, too.
Doritis is unbelievable.
He doesn't give a damn about the
non-aggression treaty nor resolving anything.
His previous request made that obvious.
I need you to hand over all
the rights to the dungeon.
If I were to lend you my
empire's military power,
it shall be beneficial for you as well.
I appreciate such a candid offer,
but I'd like to avoid the type of proposal
that could result in
losing my entire nation.
There will come a day in your future
when you shall regret those words.
Father, that might not be the
only looming threat for us.
Then the time has finally come.
Brother!
um sister hello father
Lynn
that is Lynn's father
Lynn that is the hermit's
cloak don't tell me you
went back outside the
castle again i needed to go
find the person who saved
my life myself no matter
what mmm this must be him
yes this is the one who
showed up and rescued me
last night i'm sorry for
just showing up like this
lynn here seemed to be
in quite the hurry how you
address does not matter
i do thank you for making the long
journey here so you know i'm not
like wealthy or royalty or anything
like that i don't know all the
etiquette and uh so i'm probably
going to do things wrong so sorry
in advance on the contrary i prefer
to have a real conversation at
first i would like to formally show
my gratitude without your heroic
actions my beloved daughter would
be gone forever from this world
i simply cannot thank you enough
you're welcome sire it was my honor
and a blessing to get to speak with
you all right gratitude accepted
time to hit the bath house and
head home nonetheless i cannot send
her savior away without some sort
of reward huh tell me what you'd
like whether it be land or money
it matters not ask and it shall be
yours what is it you desire friend
no i don't want anything but thank
you what i see so you have no
need for money nor land do you fair
enough how about the treasures
from the dungeon our country takes
great pride in possessing the
world's oldest dungeon all manner of
rarities have been unearthed and
are stored within the treasure hall
you can walk through our collection
of priceless relics and take
whatever you like that is far too
generous father i uh don't want any of
that either hmm i mean i don't need
any sort of gift at all your grace
what you have already granted is more
than enough so no treasures either
let's see then what can we
do i gotta get out of here
here we go what do you think of this
is that a sword weird a sword it is.
I know it doesn't look
like much at first glance.
Father, what are you doing?
It's fine, Brain. Please.
At this point, I'm afraid it has become
nothing more than a mere decoration.
This is far better than just
letting it sit here unused.
Yes, but Father!
Oh, relax.
No one will even notice if I
switch it out for the replica.
Take it.
Dang, it's super heavy.
I'm sure this must be a
family heirloom or something.
I could never accept this from you.
Oh no, no?
I simply stumbled upon
it while on a journey.
I don't even remember where.
He just found it?
It's basically a hand-me-down
Will you at least accept that?
It will make me feel better.
Of course, I graciously accept!
Good.
Good, would you like to
give it a nice solid swing?
Oh, okay.
Physical enhancements.
How's this?
It is heavy, but not so
much that I can't swing it.
Look at that, you can wield it one-handed.
Aren't you a strong, sturdy young man?
That is very kind of you, sire.
Also, about my daughter.
I would like you to teach her some things.
Toughen her up a little.
Things are getting perilous out there.
I'm rather worried about her.
You want me to? Gosh, no.
There's nothing I can teach her.
And anyway, it's something she
should, you know, decide on her own.
When parents meddle too much,
their kids kind of tend to
head in the opposite direction.
Yes, indeed.
I suppose you're right.
He sure does laugh a lot.
Well, I better hit the road.
Right.
I appreciate your time, good sir.
And as Lin's father, I
humbly thank you once again.
The heft would be great for training,
but I kind of feel like I
was given something valuable.
Oh, wait a sec. This sword.
It's about the same width as the
drain by Auntie Stella's house.
This will be great for dredging
the muck out of the sewer.
I'll try it first thing
tomorrow. Sir. Huh?
We must talk.
Don't worry, I won't take
much more of your time.
Oh, crap.
What does she want?
First of all, I'd like to
apologize for my behavior.
My conduct was not appropriate towards the
very person who saved
Lady Lindbergh's life.
I would like to ask you
for your forgiveness.
Oh, uh, no.
We don't need to do that.
And please, you should stand up, really.
Thank you for accepting my apology.
It is my sworn duty to
protect the people of the
Clays family from all
dangers they may encounter.
And you should understand that said duty
always takes precedence
over how I treat guests.
Okay.
So you are not Lynn's
maid, after all, are you?
No, I'm not.
Let me introduce myself.
I am Ines Harness, a member of the
Warrior Corps for the Clays family.
I serve as vice-captain.
Sounds like she's a big shot.
From very early in my childhood,
I have been known as the Divine Shield,
as I was appointed as the personal
royal guard of Lady Lindbergh's life.
Of course, that means I am the one
who must protect my lady at all costs,
even if it forfeits my own life.
And since you are the
person who saved her life,
it is as though you saved my life as well.
I didn't do anything all that major.
I mean it.
From here on, I shall help
you in every way possible.
If you need my assistance
with anything, let me know.
These people are really overdoing it.
Jeez, it's all a bit too
much for me, I swear.
If anything comes up, I'll ask for you.
But, let me warn you.
Lady Lindbergh may have
allowed your attitude,
demeanor, your speech, and behavior,
all unpardonable while in
audience with the king.
You are not permitted to take
on such a familiar manner.
That said,
should you continue as such, I will no
longer be able to overlook your disrespect.
Get yourself together, especially
in front of the retainers.
Right.
And I do appreciate the warning.
Okay.
Well, that's all I really
wanted to talk to you about.
Now then, to whom is it that I
find myself so deeply indebted?
I would like to have your
name, if you don't mind.
I'm Noor.
Noor!
Oh, did I do something wrong again?
No, I'm sorry. It's nothing.
Pardon, I must be taking my leave. Sure.
Great, I ticked her off again.
Is our illustrious hero
already heading home?
Oh, that's...
he's...
he's that guy.
I should know this.
You may have heard of me.
I'm Gilbert.
Won't you join me for a moment?
I would like you to show me
these wonderful talents of yours.
I just want to go home.
Oh.
Me.
Je. Me. Je.
Part.
Oh
Give me?